Autumn, the time of year where all shall fall.
In love, and take their cute boyfriends
to get a sweet potato birthday after school.
Yeah, of course they're fine.
We can't go out in our uniforms.
Don't you two walk home together, like, all the time?
Well, yeah, duh.
But this will be our first time in uniform on the train.
Still love walking home, but this is a doit.
You're getting on a train for potatoes.
Tater train.
Of course not, you worm, you bumbling buffoon.
We're doing purikura.
The holy grail of romance.
When you first got together, taking a picture was impossible.
Because photos are soul-crushing,
and I've pretty much given up on them.
But I'm chill with photo stickers.
Guess why?
Because all of those cute filters keep me from looking busted.
Oh god, that is so sad.
Seriously, learn to love yourself, girl.
Now everyone have noticed about the name of the country.
During this story jr.
We'll be right back.
恋はいつも想定外
ねえねえ聞いて
言葉を尽くして君に伝えたいの
心が体に追いついて
気付けば目で覆ってる
眼鏡を外してさ
ちゃんと目を合わせてよ
恋は走り出したの
放課後まで待ってない
大事な言葉ほど
酸素を嫌うみたい
辞書にない私なりの言葉で
早く早く
君に伝えなきゃね
ふんに薬具の記憶が
Let me guess.
Is this a school court date?
Good for you.
Jinkies.
Whatever.
Take a selfie with me.
For sure.
Why would you?
Oh, Tani wasn't a fan of that.
No, it's okay.
It's just that we see each other at school all the time, you know?
Yeah, I know.
But this is, like, different.
We had to mark it with a virtual sticky note.
You get it.
Photos are external hot drives for our memories.
I just know in the future, I'm going to want to look back on today.
It was our first date, after all, and I want to remember the fun and flirting and heart flutters.
Like a record of our love story.
I get it.
Right?
Wow, Tani boy's an easy sell.
Okay, camera eats first.
I want to take one with you in it, Tani.
Pose for your girl.
Pose how?
Ta-da!
That good!
It's super sweet potato-y, but not too sugary.
It tastes just how it looks.
I love it!
Hey!
Did you just take a picture?
I was making a face like I eat villagers!
How could you?
I thought we wanted to keep our memories for later.
Call me shallow, but I don't want you keeping the ones where I look like a clown.
What?
That seems unfair.
Well, I'd rather be unfair than I'm cute.
Hmm.
Say, uh, your skin?
Can I make another kind of shallow request?
Oh, I need to leave.
Why, hello there, my goodest sir.
Hast thou ever printed photo stickers before?
I have not.
Is there a booth that piques your interest?
Or do you just want me to pick one?
I think you know the answer to that.
Yeah, I figured.
I was just trying to be polite.
Let's strike a pose.
Make a heart.
Ha-ha!
Three, two, one.
Next, give us a little kitty cat.
Kitty cat?
Three, two, one.
Whoa.
Who's that?
Great!
Now grab each other's chins for me.
Three, two, one.
There we go.
Oh, sorry.
That was your face.
Okay.
And last but not least,
give us a great big smile.
That's so hot.
Purikura, more like put a cooler, am I right?
Yeah, that too, I guess.
Thank you, Tani.
I love him a lot.
No, where do I put this?
I want to stick it up in my room,
but I don't want my mom seeing it, you know?
Here, I'll make an album and share it with you.
Great, thanks.
Oh, you added some, too.
Yay, thanks.
Oh!
You tried to hurt.
I said kill it with fire.
I don't want to.
Look at this.
The filters didn't do anything at all to him.
I think he dodged a bullet.
I'm heading out.
Thanks, boss.
Have a good night.
Jump scare, ew!
He's still alive?
A chill overcame her as the message came in
from a love long gone cold.
This text is from an ex.
Of course he had to tack on a lull.
God forbid he opened with sorry.
Fragile masculinity at it again.
Oh, whatever.
It's the worst.
Someone you used to be close to messages you
after a hundred years of ghosting.
Then you light up for a brief second.
But then the chemistry is through the floor
and suddenly it all feels like a huge drag.
Then you think,
oh yeah, that's why this didn't work out.
It's like back to reality.
Anyway, if I look like I want to commit murder,
that's probably why.
I have no idea what she's talking about.
Why do you let them treat you that way?
Sounds sucky, but you know what?
We can override it with something epic.
Ah, bless your simplicity.
There's a lot more to being in high school than dating.
Big time agree!
We should go bowling about it.
Why bowling?
Because your girl wants to go bowling.
So you just feel like it?
I do feel like throwing something big and heavy, yes.
I feel like we've gotten off track.
Later, that very weekend!
Asuma's gonna be a little late.
She says there was a train delay.
I really thought Taira Asuma would show up together.
Hold on, that ship has not been cleared for passage.
But don't y'all get on at the same station?
Oh, too risky.
If anyone from my neighborhood saw us meeting up on the train platform for any reason...
Asuma's with him.
Oh my god, what a weird combo.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hey, there she is!
Just thinking about it makes me break into a cold sweat.
Is this your first time bowling, Tawny?
Sort of.
I came with a group when I was little.
Well, don't be shy.
Anything you want to know, I can learn ya.
Like, did you know they make the shoes so ugly as an anti-theft measure?
Vital knowledge.
They're huge.
Oakley-dokley!
Average reveal!
A hundred and eighty!
A hundred and seventy!
A hundred and thirty.
Screw you, Taira.
The hell?
I feel lucky if I hit a hundred.
Yeah, same here.
Okay!
And my average is about fifty, give or take.
What was that, you muttered?
When I wind my arm, my punch gets stronger!
Please don't refer cyclotron us.
Taira, you nerd!
I can't believe you actually got that reference!
Shut up.
Whoa!
Did you guys see that?
Nice going.
My old classmates from middle school.
They're still all hanging out together.
Why are they doing it here?
No, this is fine.
Maybe they won't notice me.
Or recognize me.
Or remember me.
Wait.
Didn't Asuma get along pretty well with them?
I really don't want to get involved with them when I'm out with these guys.
Hey, don't worry.
They're not going to come talk to you.
No?
Nah, they'll just pretend not to notice us.
Not that I mind or anything.
I just hope they're having a good time together, you know?
Wait, really?
Yeah.
Then we should too.
Not that!
Tony, you killed it!
You should be in the bowling olympic!
I just got a spare.
Hey, be safe going home!
Say bye, Yeti!
Says the next train's in ten minutes.
Kind of a long wait.
Those guys from earlier aren't going to show up in the next ten minutes, right?
Surely not.
Hey, that group bowling next to us.
Didn't you used to hang out with them back in middle school?
Huh?
Yeah, a bit.
We were close for a while, but it got kind of complicated.
Out of that group, we've got Guy 1, who's my ex, and I also had some stuff go down with Guy 2, but he doesn't count.
The brunette and the blonde, aka 3 and 4, are their new girls.
I... what?
Wait, slow down.
So there was dating and breaking up within the friend group, and because you're the ex-girlfriend, it's awkward now.
Is that right?
Hmm... well, it hasn't really been awkward on my end, but they seem to feel kind of guilty about it.
Which, what happened was, Guy 1 sent me a breakup text kind of out of nowhere, and then boom, he immediately started dating Gal 3.
I don't even say their names.
But then Guy 2 and I got a good vibe going, so I thought it was weird when he ghosted me.
Then I saw him with 4, and I was like, oh, you went after both of us at the same time, huh?
It's just a little... delicate.
This is straight-up sickening.
It actually makes my stomach churn.
How can they just shuffle partners around the same friend group like that?
It's genuinely so gross.
Add in a nuclear fallout of awkwardness, and it's the ninth circle of social hell.
Though, I ran into three on the way to the bathroom, and she was like, oh, hey, wow, long time no see.
It was a normal interaction, TBH.
No, no, no.
No, it was not!
That's a little...
One just sent me a text.
He goes, you went bowling today, right?
Lol.
Seriously?
Kind of shameless.
Yeah, his intentions are so blatant, all you can do is roll your eyes.
No, stop that.
Get angry!
Tonight?
No, all week.
First, there was the ex with his messy text.
Then there was the fake girl at bowling pretending to be your friend.
And now there's this tool casually sliding into your DMs, lol.
Not a single one of them has spoken to you like a person.
They're just pretending like nothing even happened.
It's so disrespectful.
You deserve to be angry when you're disrespected.
You're the only one getting worn down.
That can't be worth it.
Actually, you know what it is?
Once I like somebody, I just can't bring myself to unlike them.
Stuff can happen, but every time I just decide it's fine and forgive them.
Oh, that must be the reason they treat me like garbage.
So, that's it then?
You either hate their guts or let them walk all over you?
That's messed up.
That kind of stuff has always eaten at me a little bit.
But I've never really thought about it.
Never put it into words like Taita did.
Oh, whatever.
Why do you let them treat you that way?
Letting myself be a punching bag.
Or just saying I have bad luck with men.
Maybe the reality is that I need to respect myself.
Hey, Taita.
I'm sorry.
Thanks for yester-
Huh?
I'm so sorry for yesterday.
I was lying awake last night thinking who asked for your advice, you stupid animal.
If I were in your shoes, I think I'd be pissed.
But what the hell do I know?
I don't have relationships.
I'm just a spiteful little dirt.
And when I see stuff like that, I just gotta point it out.
It's a sickness.
Pointing things out?
Speaking theoretically might have been okay.
But after I thought about it, I realized it was wrong to assume I know what anyone thinks
and feels about anything.
Nope. Got it.
I got it.
I'll just say it.
It's cool.
That's cool.
Yo!
Hey, Miyu.
Your brother and your dad are going to be away for a baseball game this weekend.
No!
Sorry this was so sudden.
But it was kind of a long trip without your mic.
That's okay.
It's supposed to rain later.
Oh, is it really?
My grandma says it is.
Oh, baby.
Yes!
I love me an excuse to order delivery in the middle of the day.
We're back!
Welcome home!
You come on in, Tani!
Mom, meet Tani.
Pleasure, ma'am.
It was raised well!
I want nachos!
Heya, mamacita!
Now come inside and never leave.
Whereabouts does your family live, Tani?
The next name?
Oh, dear!
That walk must have exhausted you!
You didn't even let him finish answering!
How do you know that?
Also, if there's anything here you don't want to eat, you don't have to force yourself!
I don't care!
I didn't make it!
I don't know if she needed her to say that last part.
Oh, my goodness!
Tani, sweetie!
Do you have a favorite food?
I'm sorry!
I should have asked earlier!
Mom!
Stop interrogating him and let the boy eat!
Sorry, I'll shut up!
How about I put on some tunage?
I hear the kids like to dance-a-ku to official Hige Dance-a-ku!
Mother!
Relax!
I am begging you!
You guys need anything?
Some snacks?
Sounds good!
Thanks!
Make yourself at home!
Sorry about my mom.
I guess she's just, like, super nervous.
That was nervous?
Yeah.
Worst I've ever seen.
She's very unique.
All our interactions made me think, yep, that's your mom.
Wow!
So, like, uh, is that good or bad?
It's good.
Oh, hey!
It really did start raining!
But will it let up before you must bid us adieu?
I love being home when it's rainy out.
Such a frickin' vibe!
I love the sound.
I love how dark it gets in the middle of the day.
Rainy day at home date is so perfect!
But our summer beat the heat study sesh was perfect, too.
The chocolate and vanilla swirl of hangouts!
Oh, no.
Have I been talking too much?
Too long?
Guess I can't criticize my mom.
Say something, Connie!
Anything?
Uh, so, hey!
Mom said she'd bring us some snacks, didn't she?
What the heck do we do until then?
What do we do after?
Snack time!
Honey, I'm home!
Connie, you're back!
Yeah.
The rain was heavier than expected, so they called off the ball game.
I'm gonna go change.
No, you can't go upstairs yet!
Me, you had the boy who was a friend in our room!
Huh?
This didn't really hit me until now, but...
I have a boy in my room!
It's coming down out there!
I hope it lets up before you have to go home, though!
Yeah.
Wait, did I already say that?
What do I do?
What should I talk about?
Maybe I should just not talk?
Come over here.
So...
Hey...
Um...
I...
Wanna hug...
Don't let you go to the block!
I did, too.
Your heartbeat is insane!
I know.
Dude!
You are honestly crazy hard to read sometimes!
When you're not talking, I don't know what to say.
I'm not good with conversation.
I guess...
That's how beyond totally lame I am.
Is that okay...
With you?
Of course it is.
Tani...
Yusuke Tani...
That's me.
Yusuke...
Yu-yu...
Uh...
Oh, I'm just trying out some different things to call you.
Yu-ge!
Yu-ta-ta-tas!
Not that one.
Suzu...
Ki?
Okay, good effort.
Try again.
How about just...
Miyu.
Ah!
That works!
Miyu.
Sorry.
That's gonna take some getting used to.
Fair enough!
That's okay!
Well, that shirt sure is a blast from the past.
I figured I'd dress extra cool so I don't embarrass Miyu if I bump into her friend.
Hey, Mom!
Huh?
Tani's gonna head home so I'm gonna walk part of the...
Ah!
Oh!
Hey, Dad!
Um...
Me to a boyfriend.
Boyfriend.
Wait!
Your boyfriend?
What?
What's your name?
Tani.
No, no!
First name, please!
And thank you!
Yusuke.
Yusuke, eh?
Ha!
So, where you gonna school, kiddo?
Honey, that's enough!
We'll talk about this later!
Why?
We're just getting to know each other!
This is exactly why I didn't want them to meet!
That was a weird one.
I'm sorry you had to see my parents flipping out like that.
But apparently you found it hilarious!
Goodie!
Somehow.
I had built up all these ideas about you and your parents and your friends,
but spending time together has turned my ideas on their heads.
And now I understand you a little better.
Oh my god, that's so embarrassing!
It's like you found a Suzuki's Anatomy and you can see all my squishy insides!
Whoa.
Hey!
Finally feeling the fall!
When it stops raining in the summer, everything gets all muggy.
But the air really changes the closer you get to autumn, huh?
Yeah.
I remember the culture festival at my middle school always ended around this time of year.
So whenever I feel that wish of fall air, I think,
Ah, yet another culture festival on the books.
And honestly,
I feel like that's how I'm gonna think about it forever.
Now that you say that,
I bet that from now on,
whenever I feel the weather change,
I'll think of you.
Ah.
Geez, Tawny.
You can't say stuff like that to me.
Hm?
Because now I'm just gonna think of you too!
Is that bad?
It's gone!
My baby girl's growing up.
Hey,
what did I tell you about drinking before dinner?
Let's go!